SADIA NOOR



7903637486



sadia_noor2019@cms.ac.in



LinkedIn

ABOUT ME

Being a high-achieving student in Journalism and Mass Communication, I have acquired hands-on experience in the media field from internships and a rewarding job. These opportunities have refined my skills and deepened my insight into the ever-changing media landscape.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN JOURNALISM AND MASS COMMUNICATION

<u>Centre for Management Studies, Jain</u> (<u>Deemed-to-be</u>) <u>University</u>, Bengaluru, Karnataka

2019-2022 | Passed with Distinction

- Coordinator of <u>Melange</u> National Level Media Fest
- Member of the Media Fest Team
- Member of <u>Yuva Ignited Minds</u> A student run NGO

SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL

Notre Dame Academy, Patna, Bihar 2017-2019 | Passed with 91.8%

Arts - CBSE

- · Member of School Dance Team
- · Part of School Leadership Program
 - NDCadre

ACHIEVEMENTS



EXPERIENCE

CONSULTANT JOURNALIST

WION (IndiaDotcom Digital Pvt Ltd) | August 2022 - October 2023

- Publishing videos, creating content for livestreams as well as creating community posts for their <u>YouTube channel</u>.
- Publishing videos on the website.
- Analysing, understanding and optimising Google trends for better performance of published videos.

CONTENT EVALUATION INTERN

Wattpad India | March 2020 - November 2021

- · Analysis and evaluation of published stories on the website.
- Curating a 500 word summary of each story with added details like resemblance to other story, good and bad aspects etc.
- Judging stories as entries for different contests hosted and for Wattpad India Awards as well.

SOCIAL MEDIA INTERN

Wattpad India | January 2021 - November 2021

- Assisted in curation of different social media campaigns.
- · Assisted in curation of different marketing strategies.
- Helping in ideation of promotions of the Wattpad stories on social media platforms.

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR

Viral Fission | November 2020 - August 2021

 Performing of various tasks with different brands to increase their marketing network.

SKILLS

- Social Media Management
- Content Writing
- Academic writing
- Public speaking

- Communication
- YouTube Management
- Canva
- Content Creation